Guide to the Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records, ca. 1960-1989
Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Visual Services/Cornell Publications Photography records, ca. 1960-1989
4-3-1885
Cornell University. Publications Photography.
19 cubic ft.; 4 filing cabinets
Photographic prints and slides.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Slides of Cornell University buildings, classrooms, students, alumni, professors, athletics, and other Cornell and Ithaca, New York subjects and scenes. Photographs, ca. 1960-1980; 35 mm. black and white transparencies of historical campus photographs; 2 x 2 black and white and color slides, some identified; 35 mm. and 2 x 2 negatives, with guide; and contact sheets of prints and negatives; 8 x 10 photographs of the Theory Center; 35 mm. slides of Roberts Hall; 35 mm. slides of Maplewood Park.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Office of Visual Services was formed in the early 1960s. By the mid 1980s it was called the Cornell Office of University Relations-Visual Services. Subsequently the name was changed to Cornell University Office of Publications Services, and then to the Office of Cornell Publications.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Slides of Cornell University buildings, classrooms, students, alumni, professors, athletics, and other Cornell and Ithaca, New York subjects and scenes. Photographs, ca. 1960-1980; 35 mm. black and white transparencies of historical campus photographs; 2 x 2 black and white and color slides, some identified; 35 mm. and 2 x 2 negatives, with guide; and contact sheets of prints and negatives; 8 x 10 photographs of the Theory Center; 35 mm. slides of Roberts Hall; 35 mm. slides of Maplewood Park. Photographers included: Sol Goldberg, Russ Hamilton, and Charlie Harrington.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Publications Photography.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University--Athletics.; Cornell University--Buildings.; Cornell University--Pictorial works.
Places:
Ithaca (N.Y.)--Pictorial works.
Form and Genre Terms:
Slides (photographs).; Photographs.; Negatives.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
See also Cornell University Office of Visual Services Protest Photographs, #4-3-2093.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
The job lists indicate the date and subject of photography assignments. Assignment numbers consist of year, month, and day. Example: 7043=April 3, 1970. During the mid 1980's there was a slight change to the numbering system. During these years a leading A was used to replace the number 8. Example: A40801=August 1, 1984. Halfway through 1985, the numbering system returned to its original form. The assignment numbers refer to both the negatives and corresponding contact sheets. The contact sheets should be consulted first. If no contact sheet is in the box indicated then the negative rolls from the file cabinets can be used.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Assignments
Boxes 14-17
Series II. Slides
Boxes 1-13
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Assignments
  - Cornell in Early 1960's (Box 14)
  - November, December, January 1965
    - People out in the Snow, 659 (Box 14)
    - Rober W. Holley, Professor of Biochemistry, 658 (Box 14)
    - Blood Drive, 657 (Box 14)
    - Dorm Life and Interior of Library, 656 (Box 14)
    - President Perkins, 655 (Box 14)
  - May 1965
    - Hugh Hefner at Bailey Hall, 6551 (Box 14)
  - September 1965
    - Freshmen Convocation, 6591 (Box 14)
    - Hall of Fame, 6592 (Box 14)
    - Housing Protest, 6593 (Box 14)
  - October 1965
    - Football - Cornell vs Princeton, R1 & 2, 65101 (Box 14)
    - Football - Cornell vs Harvard, 65102 (Box 14)
    - Rockefeller Hall - Post Lab Dedication, 65103 (Box 14)
    - Football - Cornell vs, 65104 (Box 14)
    - Football - Cornell vs, R1 & 2, 65105 (Box 14)
  - December 1965
    - Basketball - Cornell vs Princeton, R1-3, 65121 (Box 14)
  - November, December, January 1966
    - Protest, 062390 (Box 14)
    - Antonie W. Blacker, Assistant Professor of Genetics, Development and Physiology, 660 (Box 14)
    - President Perkins, 665 (Box 14)
    - Event in Library, 669 (Box 14)
  - January 1966
    - Musical Performance, Mariachi Band, R2, 6611 (Box 14)
    - Outside Hut, R1-2, 6612 (Box 14)
    - Art instruction, Art exhibit, R1, R4-8, 6613 (Box 14)
  - February 1966
    - Choral performance, Hong Kong Red China border, Schoolroom, Basketball Game, Judo and Karate, R15, R16, R18-20, 6621 (Box 14)
    - Igloo in Arts Quad, 6622 (Box 14)
    - Ice Hockey, 6623 (Box 14)
    - Ice Hockey; Cornell Basketball Game, R1-2, 6624 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Basketball Game, 6625 (Box 14)
    - Mens Wrestling Match, 6626 (Box 14)
    - Ice Hockey Game, 6627 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Mens Basketball Game, R1-2, 6628 (Box 14)
  - March 1966
    - Cornell Indoor Track Meet, R3, R8, R17, 6631 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Mens Basketball Game, 6632 (Box 14)
  - May 1966
    - School of Business and Public administration, R1-27, 6650 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Latin American Year - Buffalo Philharmonic, R1 & 2, 6651 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Latin American Year - Visiting Artist, Diera, R1 & 2, 6652 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Latin American Year - Octavio Pas, Visiting Poet, R1-4, 6653 (Box 14)
    - Campus Scenes, R1-8, 6654 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Latin American Year - Opening at the Guggenheim R1-3, 6655 (Box 14)
    - R. O. T. C. Review, R1-6, 6656 (Box 14)
    - Carnegie Cup Regatta, R1 & 2, 6657 (Box 14)
  - June 1966
    - Cornell United Religious Work - father Tormey, R1-6, 6661 (Box 14)
    - Book Plate Series, R1 & 2, 6662 (Box 14)
    - Foreign Student - S. W. Karunatillake, R1-3, 6663 (Box 14)
    - Board of Trustees, 6664 (Box 14)
    - Commencement, R1-6, 6665 (Box 14)
    - Madame White at Uris Library, with Her Portrait, R1-3, 6666 (Box 14)
    - President Perkins at his Child's Commencement at Cayuga Heights School, R1 & 2, 6667 (Box 14)
    - Lou Montgomery, Track Coach, Testimonial at Moakley House, 6668 (Box 14)
  - July 1966
    - Langmuir Lab Exteriors, R 1 & 2, 6671 (Box 14)
  - August 1966
    - Uris Library, R1-13, 6681 (Box 14)
    - Ned Flash, Wearing Cornell Gown, R 1 & 2, 6682 (Box 14)
    - Cornell University Athletic Association - Wood and Gogolak, R 1-3, 6683 (Box 14)
    - Cornell University Athletic Association - Jack Musick, 6684 (Box 14)
    - Upward Bound' Program, R 1-12, 6685 (Box 14)
    - Interior Shots, Steve Muller's Office, 6686 (Box 14)
    - United Fund, R1-6, 6691 (Box 14)
  - September 1966
    - Morrill Hall, 6692 (Box 14)
    - Thomas Gold, Astronomy, Radiophysics, R1-4, 6693 (Box 14)
    - Candids of President Perkins at Willard Straight Hall, 6694 (Box 14)
    - Drug conference - Goddard, Turner, etc., and Hyperbola, R1-7, 6695 (Box 14)
    - Board of Trustees, (7 4X5, 66101 (Box 14)
  - October 1966
    - John Olin and Mary Donlon, R1-7, 66102 (Box 14)
    - Rockwell collection at A.D.White Art Museum, 66103 (Box 14)
    - Wordsworth People at Olin Library, 66104 (Box 14)
    - Baker Laboratory, (for University Publications, 66105 (Box 14)
    - Professor Conway, Engineering and Tape Experiments, R 1 & 2, 66106 (Box 14)
    - Society for the Humanities, Raymon aaron and VIPs, R1-4, 66107 (Box 14)
    - Football - Cornell vs Dartmouth, 66108 (Box 14)
    - Football - Cornell vs Penn, 66109 (Box 14)
  - November 1966
    - Sperry Dedication, University Halls, R1-3, 66111 (Box 14)
    - Nutrition series, Savage Hall, R1-12, 66112 (Box 14)
    - Kramer Collection at the Art Museum, 66113 (Box 14)
    - Baker Laboratory, R1-10, 66114 (Box 14)
    - Coach Musick at Home, R1-3, 66115 (Box 14)
  - December 1966
    - Foreign Student, G. Babatunde, R1-4, 66121 (Box 14)
  - January 1967
    - Synchrotron, R1-3, 6711 (Box 14)
    - Robert Sproull, Office Interiors, R1 & 2, 6712 (Box 14)
    - School of Architecture, New York City, R1-17, 6713 (Box 14)
  - February 1967
    - Sperry Plaque, 6721 (Box 14)
    - Art: USA Exhibit, R1-2, 6722 (Box 14)
    - Cornell University Athletic Association Awards Banquet, 6723 (Box 14)
    - Foreign Students on Tour, 6724 (Box 14)
    - Archbishop Camara - visitor, R1-3, 6725 (Box 14)
    - Williamsburg - President Perkins Presides at International Conference of Education, (4 X 5 negatives, 6726 (Box 14)
    - Williamsburg - President Perkins Presides at International Conference of Education, R1-11, 6727 (Box 14)
    - Basketball - Cornell vs Yale, R1 & 2, 6728 (Box 14)
    - Williamsburg - President Perkins Presides at International Conference on Education, R1 & 2, 6729 (Box 14)
  - March 1967
    - Harlem Kids Visit Campus, their Art Exhibit at Willard Straight Hall, R1-11, 6731 (Box 14)
    - Industrial and Labor Relations School, R1-22, 6732 (Box 14)
    - Draft Card Soliciting, R1 & 2, 6733 (Box 14)
    - Secretary of State Dean Rusk Visits Cornell, r1-4, 6734 (Box 14)
    - Jim Dine - Artist, R1 & 2, 6735 (Box 14)
    - Secretary of State Dean Rusk, Kodacolor, 6736 (Box 14)
    - Heptagonals, 1967, R1 & 2, 6737 (Box 14)
  - April 1967
    - Memorial Service for Victims of residential Club Fire, 6741 (Box 14)
    - Spring Mobilization, 6742 (Box 14)
    - We Love You, Proctor George, R1 & 2, 6743 (Box 14)
    - Glee Club - Hampton, 6744 (Box 14)
    - Glee Club Rehersal, 6745 (Box 14)
    - Glee Club, R1 & 2, 6746 (Box 14)
  - May 1967
    - Deans of all Cornell Schools, Group Shot, (4 X 5 negatives, 6751 (Box 14)
    - Architecture Class Project - Cans, R1 & 2, 6752 (Box 14)
    - ROTC Review, R1 & 2, 6753 (Box 14)
    - Van Alan Clark and President Perkins, color, 6754 (Box 14)
  - June 1967
    - Pooch Pagent and Concern, 6761 (Box 14)
    - Joseph Ebel (Student) and Family, R1 & 2, 6762 (Box 14)
    - Columbus Book - Rare Book, 6763 (Box 14)
    - Reunion - Crews, 6764 (Box 14)
    - Reunion - Crews, color, 6765 (Box 14)
    - Cosmic House in the Danby Hills, R1-4, 6766 (Box 14)
  - July 1967
    - Goldwin Smith Hall, R1, 6771 (Box 14)
    - Executive Program, B & P A, R1-14, 6772 (Box 14)
    - I & L R, R1-3, 6773 (Box 14)
    - John Burton, r1, 6774 (Box 14)
  - September 1967
    - Jack Kiely and Family (Mayor of Ithaca), R1-3, 6791 (Box 14)
    - Freshmen Orientation, R1-10, 6792 (Box 14)
    - Cornell University Medical Colege, R1-13, 6793 (Box 14)
    - Research Pictures, R1-3, 6794 (Box 14)
  - October 1967
    - Space Sciences Building, R1, 67101 (Box 14)
    - Council Weekend, Kauffman Dedication, mcMaster's Exhibit, R1-5, R7, 67102 (Box 14)
    - Hans Bethe, Nobel Prize Winner, R1-12, 67103 (Box 14)
    - Alcoa Art Exhibit at Cornell, R1-8, 67104 (Box 14)
    - President Perkins at Colonial Williamsburg - President Johnson's Conference on Higher Education, R1-15, 67105 (Box 14)
  - November 1967
    - President James Perkins and Staff, R1-4, 67111 (Box 14)
    - Demonstration - Marines, R1 & 2, 67112 (Box 14)
    - Glee Club Feature - Pre-abroad Tour, R1-4, 67113 (Box 14)
    - Glen Series - Professor MacDaniel, R1-3, 67114 (Box 14)
    - Model Dorm Rooms at Engineering School, R1, 67115 (Box 14)
    - Hotel School Feature, R1, 67116 (Box 14)
  - December 1967
    - Scheetz Dinner, R1-3, 67121 (Box 14)
    - Scheetz Dinner, Kodacolor, R1, 67122 (Box 14)
  - January 1968
    - Professor Series, Endowed, R1-13, 6811 (Box 14)
  - February 1968
    - Professor Series, Endowed, R1-23, 6821 (Box 14)
    - Cornell University Athletic Association Awards, R1-3, 6822 (Box 14)
    - Cornell vs Princeton - Basketball, R1 & 2, 6823 (Box 14)
    - Visiting Professors, Sweden, Vet School, R1, 6824 (Box 14)
    - R.O.T.C., R1-3, 6825 (Box 14)
    - Law School, R1-15, 6826 (Box 14)
    - Snow Scenes, R1 & 2, 6827 (Box 14)
    - President Perkins, R1-3, 6828 (Box 14)
    - Cornell vs, Hockey, R1 & 2, 6829 (Box 14)
  - March 1968
    - Heptagonals, R1, 6831 (Box 14)
    - Wilson Synchrotron, R1, 6832 (Box 14)
    - Convocation, R1-12, 6833 (Box 14)
    - North Campus Ground Breaking, R1, 6834 (Box 14)
    - Anthony Eden, Prime Minister of Great Britain, R1 & 2, 6835 (Box 14)
    - Urie Bronfenbrenner, Professor of Psychology and Human Development, 6836 (Box 14)
  - April 1968
    - Arecibo Radio/Radar Telescope, R1-18, 6841 (Box 14)
    - Arecibo Radio/Radar Telescope, Color, 6842 (Box 14)
    - Memorial and Teach-in, R1-3, 6843 (Box 14)
    - Thomas Gold, Professor of Astronomy, Director, Radiophysics Space Research, R1-3, 6844 (Box 14)
    - Campus Scenes, R1-5, R7-14, R16-20, 6845 (Box 14)
    - Manila Kids, R1-3, 6846 (Box 14)
  - May 1968
    - Inside Cornell, R1-8, 6851 (Box 14)
    - Architects Retiring, 6852 (Box 14)
    - Outside Cornell, R1-12, 6853 (Box 14)
    - Hotel School - Cullen, 6854 (Box 14)
    - Professors Lei and Fei, R1 & 2, 6855 (Box 14)
    - Joseph N. Pew and Family at Cornell, R1-8, 6856 (Box 14)
    - Chicago Professors, 6857 (Box 14)
    - National Science Writers Visit Cornell, R1 & 2, 6858 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Glee Club, 6859 (Box 14)
    - Alex Kira, Architecture, 68510 (Box 14)
  - June 1968
    - Tower Club, 6861 (Box 14)
    - Graduation, R1-8, 6862 (Box 14)
    - Alumni, R1-5, 6863 (Box 14)
    - Walter Lefeber, 6864 (Box 14)
    - Girl Chimesmasters, 6865 (Box 14)
    - Clock tower and Graduate Playing Chimes, R1 & 2, 6866 (Box 14)
  - July 1968
    - Wilson Synchrotron, R1-15, R16-32, 6871 (Box 14)
    - Alumni University, R1-11, 6873 (Box 14)
  - August 1968
    - Victor Colby, Professor of Art, 6881 (Box 14)
  - September 1968
    - Horse and Synchrotron, 6891 (Box 14)
    - Hans Bethe on Mini Bike, R1 & 2, 6892 (Box 14)
    - Gannett Clinic, Exteriors and Interiors, R1 & 2, 6893 (Box 14)
  - October 1968
    - Cornell Football, vs Colgate, 68101 (Box 14)
    - Sculptures on the Arts Quad, by visiting artist, 68102 (Box 14)
    - Thomas Gold, Professor, 68103 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Trustees and model, 68104 (Box 14)
    - Trustee Council Weekend/Dedication of Wilson Synchrotron, 68105 (Box 14)
    - Time Machine, 68106 (Box 14)
    - Radiation Biology, 68107 (Box 14)
    - Dr. Wasserman, 68108 (Box 14)
  - November 1968
    - Professor Rossiter with Hat, 68111 (Box 14)
    - Home Economics, 68112 (Box 14)
    - Robert Moog with Synthesizer in Trumansburg Studio, 68113 (Box 14)
    - Lab of Ornithology for New York Times, 68114 (Box 14)
    - Sick Crane at Lab of Ornithology, 68115 (Box 14)
    - Seager, Room Dedication at Uris, 68116 (Box 14)
    - Old Olin Interiors, 68117 (Box 14)
  - December 1968
    - Bradfields at Dedication of Bradfield Hall, 68121 (Box 14)
    - Dean Dinner, 68122 (Box 14)
    - Professor Cade with Falcon at Ornithology Lab, 68123 (Box 14)
  - January 1969
    - Human ecology, 6910 (Box 14)
    - George Healey and Rare Books at Uris Library, 6911 (Box 14)
    - Duck Innoculation, 6912 (Box 14)
    - College Bowl participants, 6913 (Box 14)
    - Gottfried Schatz, Helmut Plattner, of Bio-Chem and Applied Physics, 6914 (Box 14)
    - Hotel Automation, 6915 (Box 14)
    - Snowball fight outside Donlon Hall, 6916 (Box 14)
    - Campus Scenes, 6917 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Trustees '69, 6918 (Box 14)
    - Alfred Kahn, 6919 (Box 14)
    - Intersession Program on Women January 22-25, 1969, at MVR, 69110 (Box 14)
    - Tunisian students, 69111J (Box 14)
    - Construction of Campus Store - hole in the ground, 69112J (Box 14)
    - Long & Rathjens, 69113J (Box 14)
    - Teaching assistants, 69114J (Box 14)
    - Mrs. Spencer and baby, 69115J (Box 14)
  - February 1969
    - Basketball and Jerry Lace, 6921 (Box 14)
    - Registration, Spring '69, 6922 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Alumni University faculty, 6923 (Box 14)
    - School of Veterinary Medicine - intensive care unit, 6924 (Box 14)
    - University Deans - group shot, 6925 (Box 14)
    - Earth Artists at A.D.White Museum, 6926 (Box 14)
    - Muhammed Ali at Bailey Auditorium, 6927 (Box 14)
    - S D S Housing demonstrations, R1 & 2 - 2/69; R3 & 4 - 3/69, 6928 (Box 14)
    - Cornell President Dale Corson, 6929 (Box 14)
    - Attorney General Ramsey Clark at Law School, 69210 (Box 14)
    - Malcolm X Day demonstration on Olin Libe steps, 69211 (Box 14)
    - Heptagonals - R1-5 Sol; R6-12 Pat Crowe, 69212 (Box 14)
    - Brian Tierney R1; Michael Sienko R2, 69213 (Box 14)
    - Hockey - Cornell vs Harvard, 69214 (Box 14)
  - March 1969
    - House owned by Cornell University, 6931 (Box 14)
    - Hotel School student from Cameroon, 6932 (Box 14)
    - Convocation, 6933 (Box 14)
    - G. E. Check, 6934 (Box 14)
    - Green Dragon Parade/St. Patrick's Day/Air filled sculptures by Architecture students, 6935 (Box 14)
    - David Seidman, engineering, 6936 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Crew, 6937 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Savoyards' Mikado by Gilbert & Sullivan, 6938 (Box 14)
    - Quentin Gibson, Bio Chemistry, 6939 (Box 14)
    - Girl and Easter Egg, 69310 (Box 14)
    - ROTC Protest, Marine Recruiters, 69311 (Box 14)
    - Tower Chimes and lightening rod, 69312 (Box 14)
    - Raymond Aaron and VIP's, 69313 (Box 14)
    - Freilicher, 69314 (Box 14)
  - April 1969
    - New Dorms on North Campus, 6941 (Box 14)
    - Susan Livingstone, 6942 (Box 14)
    - Parabola for Bird Recording, 6943 (Box 14)
    - Hubbell's Cloud - Architecture, 6944 (Box 14)
    - Turner, 6945 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Fencing, 6946 (Box 14)
    - Councilor Library, 6947 (Box 14)
    - Ecologists on Cayuga Lake, 6948 (Box 14)
    - Pike Week - Student fun and games, 6949 (Box 14)
    - Newman Hall, 69410 (Box 14)
    - Professor Ackerman and Stu Brown, Arts Quad demonstration, 69411 (Box 14)
    - Red Cross Blood mobile, 69412 (Box 14)
    - Black Students takeover, Willart Straight, Barton Hall, etc., 69413 (Box 14)
    - Hotel Ezra Cornell, 69414 (Box 14)
  - May 1969
    - Carnegie Cup Crew Race, 6951 (Box 14)
    - Library Vase, 6952 (Box 14)
    - S D S vs R O T C, 6953 (Box 14)
    - Newman Hall with Fisheye lens, 6954 (Box 14)
    - Karel Husa, Professor, 6955 (Box 14)
    - Soft Sculpture at the A.D.White Museum, 6956 (Box 14)
    - Spring Arts Quad Show, 6957 (Box 14)
    - Cyrus Eaton visits Cornell, 6958 (Box 14)
    - Professor Fuchs, 6959 (Box 14)
    - Low Income Housing model, 69510 (Box 14)
    - Constituent assembly, 69511 (Box 14)
    - Professor ralph Meek, Hotel School, 69512 (Box 14)
    - Professor Thomas Gold, 69513 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Tower Club, 69514 (Box 14)
    - AHMA Day, 69515 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Lacrosse, 69516 (Box 14)
    - Professor Milton Konvitz, 69517 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Crew vs Penn, 69518 (Box 14)
    - Judo, 69519 (Box 14)
    - Ivy League Coaches, 69520 (Box 14)
    - Cornell baseball, 69521 (Box 14)
    - Fuertes room, Lab of Ornithology, 69522 (Box 14)
    - Professor Frank Drake, 69523 (Box 14)
  - June 1969
    - Campus Scenes, 6960 (Box 14)
    - Campus Scenes, Pat Crowe, R1-25, 6961 (Box 14)
    - John Hsu, Professor, 6962 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Centennial '63, 6963 (Box 14)
    - Deer, 6964 (Box 14)
    - Campus Living, 6965 (Box 14)
    - Commencement R1-5, 6967 (Box 14)
    - Commencement R1-6, 6968 (Box 14)
    - Reunion R1-2, R5-8, R11-16, 69610 (Box 14)
  - July 1969
    - Mrs. Elizabeth McLellan, 6971 (Box 14)
    - Summer Registration, 6972 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Alumni University, R1-6 P. Crowe; R7-13 Sol, 6973 (Box 14)
    - Mrs. Scheetz, 6974 (Box 14)
    - Telephone Switchboard, 6975 (Box 14)
  - August 1969
    - Professor Jason Seley with his sculpture, 6981 (Box 14)
  - September 1969
    - Professor Hans H. Muxfeldt, Chemistry, 6991 (Box 14)
    - President Dale Corson, 6992 (Box 14)
    - Cornell football practice, 6993 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Registration, 6994 (Box 14)
    - Bugliari and Kisker, 6995 (Box 14)
    - Lyle Carter, 6996 (Box 14)
    - Arrival of Moon dust sample for testing, Thomas Gold and Professor Morrison, 6997 (Box 14)
    - Humphrey Service building dedication, 6998 (Box 14)
    - Terence Cool, Thermal engineering, 6999 (Box 14)
    - United Fund drive, 69910 (Box 14)
    - Installation of Quad lights, 69911 (Box 14)
    - Alice Cook, 69912 (Box 14)
    - W. Donald Cooke, 69913 (Box 14)
    - North Campus residential complex, 69914 (Box 14)
    - Cornell football vs Colgate, 69915 (Box 14)
  - October 1969
    - End the Vietnam War - Moratorium, 69101 (Box 14)
    - Cornell water polo, 69102 (Box 14)
    - Rukudzo Murapa, African student, 69103 (Box 14)
    - Hotel School; R1-frozen food; R2-hotel room, 69104 (Box 14)
    - Paul Schoelkopf house dedication, 69105 (Box 14)
    - Ted Morris, 69106 (Box 14)
    - Clinton Rossiter, Government, 69107 (Box 14)
    - Constituent Assembly meeting at Martha Van, 69108 (Box 14)
    - Homecoming '69, 69109 (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes by Harvey Weber, 691011 (Box 14)
    - Jack Hudson, Zoology, 691012 (Box 14)
    - Frank Long, 691013 (Box 14)
    - Rabbi Goldfarb and friends, 691014 (Box 14)
  - November 1969
    - B & P A class housing off campus, 69111 (Box 14)
    - Synchrotron un-dedication - dismantling of original, 69112 (Box 14)
    - Ezra and Candace Cornell, descendants, 69113 (Box 14)
    - Cheerleaders, (Schulman, 69114 (Box 14)
    - Cornell basketball vs Penn, 69115 (Box 14)
    - ROTC demonstration, 69116 (Box 14)
    - Annabel Taylor Chapel (Schulman, 69117 (Box 14)
    - 6 year PhD student (L. Baum, 69118 (Box 14)
    - Ornithologists conference (Schulman, 69119 (Box 14)
    - C. Dalton Jones, Aficana Studies, 691110 (Box 14)
    - Leeming interview - ROTC - Student heads (Schulman, 691111 (Box 14)
    - Music group, recorders, outdoors, 691112 (Box 14)
    - Arts Quad Peace Vigil, 691113 (Box 14)
    - Hot chestnuts, 691114 (Box 14)
    - J. Congress Mbata, Africana Studies, 691115 (Box 14)
  - December 1969
    - Alan Funt, Candid Camera, 69121 (Box 14)
    - Fraternity Presidents, etc. (Schulman, 69122 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Hockey, 69123 (Box 14)
    - Cornell basketball vs Columbia, 69124 (Box 14)
    - Woman scorekeeper - wrestling, 69125 (Box 14)
    - Thomas Eisner (Schulman, 69126 (Box 14)
    - Electric car motor, 69127 (Box 14)
    - Carson Carr, 69128 (Box 14)
    - Christmas tree, 69129 (Box 14)
    - Dale Corson R1 & 2, 691210 (Box 14)
    - Education Policy committee - students, 691211 (Box 14)
    - ROTC officers, 691212 (Box 14)
    - Alumni University faculty, 691213 (Box 14)
    - Snow scenes, 691214 (Box 14)
  - January 1970
    - Treasurer's Office, Lew Durland, Robert Horn, etc., 7011 (Box 14)
    - Snow Scenes, 7012 (Box 14)
    - Snowblower, 7013 (Box 14)
    - Class officers, 7014 (Box 14)
    - Gonnie Brier '72, counselor, 7015 (Box 14)
    - Exam clinic at Willard Straight, 7016 (Box 14)
    - Exams and aftermath, 7017 (Box 14)
    - Gamma Ray Telescope/S. Goldberg, 7018 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Glee club in Germany, 7019 (Box 14)
    - Tree removal, 70110 (Box 14)
    - Gary Lee, 70111 (Box 14)
    - Physical Fitness - Teagle, 70112 (Box 14)
    - Professor Whyte, 70113 (Box 14)
  - February 1970
    - January registration, 7021 (Box 14)
    - Felix Reichmann, Olin Library, 7022 (Box 14)
    - Ezra Cornell, TV, Treasurer's office, 7023 (Box 14)
    - Cornell vs Penn, TV, 7024 (Box 14)
    - University Ombudsman, 7025 (Box 14)
    - Willard Straight tree stump, 7026 (Box 14)
    - Electron Microscope, 7027 (Box 14)
    - Cascadilla Hall, 7028 (Box 14)
    - Suspension bridge at night; traffic outside Willard Straight, 7029 (Box 14)
    - Fat Tuesday, student activities at Annabel Taylor, 70210 (Box 14)
    - Tiddlywinks contest at Willard Straight, 70211 (Box 14)
    - Glass blower at Clark hall, 70212 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, University Trustees, 70213 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Hockey vs. Boston college, 70214 (Box 14)
    - Ornithology stamps, 70215 (Box 14)
    - Cornell rifle team, 70216 (Box 14)
    - Dr. Richard O'Brien, Bio Sciences, 70217 (Box 14)
    - North Campus dorms, 70218 (Box 14)
    - Crystal growing at Clark, 70219 (Box 14)
  - March 1970
    - Gymnastic, 7031 (Box 14)